Alright the drink we're about to make is Alien Secretion.
Mm, sounds good doesn't it?
Here we go.
This is how you make it.
Put ice in a glass and do one shot of melon liqueur, that green alien color, very important ingredient.
And follow that up with a shot of Malibu Rum.
And finally, going to top it off with some pineapple juice.
It'll be about a shot of pineapple juice.
And mix this together.
Now I know Alien Secretion doesn't really sound all that great.
But this drink actually tastes fantastic.
You can tell by the ingredients and the smell that it's going to be good.
So, grab an alien, squeeze out a little bit of Alien Secretion.
Look at that color, beautiful.
Give it a straw and secrete it in to your mouth.
Bottoms up.